Guide to the University of Pittsburgh Archives Moving Images Collection, ca. 1928-2001 UA.Film.Video
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Sports, I.
  - Football, 3.
    - Film, 957 items
      - 1983 #8 Maryland vs. Pitt (Defense #2), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 675)
      - 1983 #9 West Virginia vs. Pitt (Offense #1), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 522)
      - 1983 #9 West Virginia vs. Pitt (Defense #1), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 509)
      - 1983 #9 West Virginia vs. Pitt (Defense #1), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 518)
      - 1983 #9 West Virginia vs. Pitt (Offense #2), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 521)
      - 1983 #9 West Virginia vs. Pitt (Defense #2), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 519)
      - 1983 #9 West Virginia vs. Pitt (Defense #2), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 517)
      - 1983 #10 Louisville vs. Pitt (Offense #1), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 513)
      - 1983 #10 Louisville vs. Pitt (Offense #1), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 690)
      - 1983 #10 Louisville vs. Pitt (Defense #1), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 683)
      - 1983 #10 Louisville vs. Pitt (Defense #1), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 692)
      - 1983 #10 Louisville vs. Pitt (Offense #2), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 514)
      - 1983 #10 Louisville vs. Pitt (Offense #2), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 691)
      - 1983 #10 Louisville vs. Pitt (Defense #2), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 689)
      - 1983 #10 Louisville vs. Pitt (Defense #2), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 693)
      - 1983 #11 Navy vs. Pitt (Offense #1), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 435)
      - 1983 #11 Navy vs. Pitt (Defense #1), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 520)
      - 1983 #11 Navy vs. Pitt (Offense #2), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 431)
      - 1983 #11 Navy vs. Pitt (Defense #2), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 657)
      - 1983 #11 Navy vs. Pitt (Kicking), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 436)
      - 1984 #1 Temple vs. Pitt (Offense #1), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 708)
      - 1984 #1 Temple vs. Pitt (Offense #1), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 709)
      - 1984 #1 Temple vs. Pitt (Defense #1), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 711)
      - 1984 #1 Temple vs. Pitt (Defense #1-Interior Line), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 713)
      - 1984 #1 Temple vs. Pitt (Offense #2), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 707)
      - 1984 #1 Temple vs. Pitt (Offense #2), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 710)
      - 1984 #1 Temple vs. Pitt (Offense #2-Interior Line), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 714)
      - 1984 #1 Temple vs. Pitt (Defense #2), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 712)
      - 1984 #1 Temple vs. Pitt (Defense #2-Interior Line), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 704)
      - 1984 Brigham Young vs. Pitt (Offense #1), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 697)
      - 1984 Brigham Young vs. Pitt (Offense #2), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 698)
      - 1984 Brigham Young vs. Pitt (Kicking), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 699)
      - 1984 East Carolina vs. Pitt (Offense #1), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 539)
      - 1984 East Carolina vs. Pitt (Defense #1), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 534)
      - 1984 East Carolina vs. Pitt (Offense #2), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 535)
      - 1984 East Carolina vs. Pitt (Defense #2), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 533)
      - 1984 East Carolina vs. Pitt (Kicking), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 532)
      - 1984 Miami vs. Pitt (Offense #1), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 525)
      - 1984 Miami vs. Pitt (Offense #2), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 526)
      - 1984 Miami vs. Pitt (Kicking), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 524)
      - 1984 Navy vs. Pitt (Kicking), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 503)
      - 1984 Ohio State vs. Pitt-Fiesta Bowl (Offense #1), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 676)
      - 1984 Ohio State vs. Pitt-Fiesta Bowl (Offense #1-Interior Line), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 540)
      - 1984 Ohio State vs. Pitt-Fiesta Bowl (Offense #2), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 677)
      - 1984 Ohio State vs. Pitt-Fiesta Bowl XIII (Kicking), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 530)
      - 1984 Oklahoma vs. Pitt (Kicking), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 531)
      - 1984 Penn State vs. Pitt (Offense #1), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 537)
      - 1984 Penn State vs. Pitt (Offense #2), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 538)
      - 1984 South Carolina vs. Pitt (Offense #1), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 504)
      - 1984 South Carolina vs. Pitt (Defense #1), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 505)
      - 1984 South Carolina vs. Pitt (Offense #2), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 680)
      - 1984 South Carolina vs. Pitt (Defense #2), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 506)
      - 1984 South Carolina vs. Pitt (Kicking), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 682)
      - 1984 Syracuse vs. Pitt (Offense #1), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 672)
      - 1984 Syracuse vs. Pitt (Defense #1), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 678)
      - 1984 Syracuse vs. Pitt (Offense #2), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 681)
      - 1984 Syracuse vs. Pitt (Defense #2), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 523)
      - 1984 Syracuse vs. Pitt (Kicking), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 679)
      - 1984 Tulane vs. Pitt (Offense #1), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 700)
      - 1984 Tulane vs. Pitt (Offense #1-Interior Line), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 694)
      - 1984 Tulane vs. Pitt (Defense #1), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 702)
      - 1984 Tulane vs. Pitt (Defense #1-Interior Line), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 695)
      - 1984 Tulane vs. Pitt (Offense #2), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 701)
      - 1984 Tulane vs. Pitt (Defense #2), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 703)
      - 1984 Tulane vs. Pitt (Kicking), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 696)
      - 1984 West Virginia vs. Pitt (Offense #1), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 527)
      - 1984 West Virginia vs. Pitt (Offense #1-Interior Line), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 705)
      - 1984 West Virginia vs. Pitt (Defense #1), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 529)
      - 1984 West Virginia vs. Pitt (Offense #2), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 528)
      - 1984 West Virginia vs. Pitt (Offense #2-Interior Line), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 536)
      - 1984 West Virginia vs. Pitt (Kicking), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 706)
      - 1985 Boston College vs. Pitt (Kicking), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 562)
      - 1985 North Carolina State vs. Pitt (Offense #1), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 720)
      - 1985 North Carolina State vs. Pitt (Defense #1), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 725)
      - 1985 North Carolina State vs. Pitt (Defense #1-Interior Line), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 722)
      - 1985 North Carolina State vs. Pitt (Defense #2), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 724)
      - 1985 North Carolina State vs. Pitt (Defense #2-Interior Line), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 723)
      - 1985 Ohio State vs. Pitt (Offense #1), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 730)
      - 1985 Ohio State vs. Pitt (Defense #1), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 718)
      - 1985 Ohio State vs. Pitt (Offense #2), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 721)
      - 1985 Ohio State vs. Pitt (Offense #2), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 719)
      - 1985 Ohio State vs. Pitt (Defense #2), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 716)
      - 1985 Ohio State vs. Pitt (Kicking), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 717)
      - 1985 Penn State vs. Pitt (Defense #1), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 549)
      - 1985 Penn State vs. Pitt (Defense #2), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 550)
      - 1985 Penn State vs. Pitt (Kicking), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 544)
      - 1985 Penn State vs. Pitt (Kicking-end zone), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 551)
      - 1985 Rutgers vs. Pitt (Offense #1), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 735)
      - 1985 Rutgers vs. Pitt (Defense #1), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 732)
      - 1985 Rutgers vs. Pitt (Offense #2), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 731)
      - 1985 Rutgers vs. Pitt (Defense #2), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 733)
      - 1985 Rutgers vs. Pitt (Kicking), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 715)
      - 1985 South Carolina vs. Pitt (Offense #1), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 734)
      - 1985 South Carolina vs. Pitt (Defense #1), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 727)
      - 1985 South Carolina vs. Pitt (Defense #1-Interior Line), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 729)
      - 1985 South Carolina vs. Pitt (Offense #2), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 726)
      - 1985 South Carolina vs. Pitt (Defense #2), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 728)
      - 1985 South Carolina vs. Pitt (Defense #2-Interior Line), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 558)
      - 1985 South Carolina vs. Pitt (Kicking), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 546)
      - 1985 Syracuse vs. Pitt (Offense #1), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 582)
      - 1985 Syracuse vs. Pitt (Defense #1), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 584)
      - 1985 Syracuse vs. Pitt (Offense #2), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 583)
      - 1985 Syracuse vs. Pitt (Defense #2), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 547)
      - 1985 Syracuse vs. Pitt (Defense #2-Interior Line), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 548)
      - 1985 Syracuse vs. Pitt (Defense #2-Interior Line), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 555)
      - 1985 Syracuse vs. Pitt (Kicking), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 556)
      - 1985 Temple vs. Pitt (Offense #1), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 545)
      - 1985 Temple vs. Pitt (Defense #1), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 542)
      - 1985 Temple vs. Pitt (Offense #2), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 541)
      - 1985 Temple vs. Pitt (Defense #2), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 543)
      - 1985 West Virginia vs. Pitt (Offense #1), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 552)
      - 1985 West Virginia vs. Pitt (Defense #1), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 554)
      - 1985 West Virginia vs. Pitt (Defense #2-Interior Line), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 561)
      - 1985 West Virginia vs. Pitt (Offense #2), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 553)
      - 1985 West Virginia vs. Pitt (Defense #2), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 560)
      - 1985 West Virginia vs. Pitt (Defense #2-Interior Line), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 559)
      - 1985 West Virginia vs. Pitt (Kicking), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 557)
      - 1986 Maryland vs. Pitt (Defense #2-end zone), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/4 (Box 42, Reel 763)
      - 1986 Maryland vs. Pitt (Kicking), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/4 (Box 42, Reel 762)
      - 1986 Miami vs. Pitt (Offense #1), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 736)
      - 1986 Miami vs. Pitt (Offense #2), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 749)
      - 1986 Miami vs. Pitt (Defense #2), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 748)
      - 1986 Miami vs. Pitt (Kicking), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 747)
      - 1986 Navy vs. Pitt (Defense #2-End Zone IV), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 569)
      - 1986 Navy vs. Pitt (Kicking), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 570)
      - 1986 North Carolina State vs. Pitt (Offense #1), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 742)
      - 1986 North Carolina State vs. Pitt (Offense #1), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 751)
      - 1986 North Carolina State vs. Pitt (Defense #1), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 746)
      - 1986 North Carolina State vs. Pitt (Defense #1), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 753)
      - 1986 North Carolina State vs. Pitt (Offense #2), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 741)
      - 1986 North Carolina State vs. Pitt (Offense #2), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 750)
      - 1986 North Carolina State vs. Pitt (Defense #2), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 737)
      - 1986 North Carolina State vs. Pitt (Defense #2), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 754)
      - 1986 North Carolina State vs. Pitt (Kicking), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 752)
      - 1986 Notre Dame vs. Pitt (Offense #1), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 745)
      - 1986 Notre Dame vs. Pitt (Defense #1), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 571)
      - 1986 Notre Dame vs. Pitt (Offense #2), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 563)
      - 1986 Notre Dame vs. Pitt (Defense #2), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 572)
      - 1986 Notre Dame vs. Pitt (Kicking), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 573)
      - 1986 Penn State vs. Pitt (Offense #1), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 568)
      - 1986 Penn State vs. Pitt (Offense #2), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 739)
      - 1986 Penn State vs. Pitt (Kicking), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 740)
      - 1986 Purdue vs. Pitt (Offense #1), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/4 (Box 42, Reel 772)
      - 1986 Purdue vs. Pitt (Defense #1), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/4 (Box 42, Reel 774)
      - 1986 Purdue vs. Pitt (Offense #2), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/4 (Box 42, Reel 773)
      - 1986 Purdue vs. Pitt (Defense #2), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/4 (Box 42, Reel 775)
      - 1986 Purdue vs. Pitt (Kicking), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/4 (Box 42, Reel 776)
      - 1986 Rutgers vs. Pitt (Offense #1), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 564)
      - 1986 Rutgers vs. Pitt (Defense #1), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 566)
      - 1986 Rutgers vs. Pitt (Offense #2), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 565)
      - 1986 Rutgers vs. Pitt (Defense #2), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 567)
      - 1986 Rutgers vs. Pitt (Defense #2-End Zone III), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 580)
      - 1986 Rutgers vs. Pitt (Kicking), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 581)
      - 1986 Syracuse vs. Pitt (Offense #1), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/4 (Box 42, Reel 764)
      - 1986 Syracuse vs. Pitt (Defense #1), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 577)
      - 1986 Syracuse vs. Pitt (Offense #2), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 578)
      - 1986 Syracuse vs. Pitt (Defense #2), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 576)
      - 1986 Syracuse vs. Pitt (Kicking), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 575)
      - 1986 Temple vs. Pitt (Offense #1), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/4 (Box 42, Reel 756)
      - 1986 Temple vs. Pitt (Offense #1), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/4 (Box 42, Reel 760)
      - 1986 Temple vs. Pitt (Defense #1), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/4 (Box 42, Reel 758)
      - 1986 Temple vs. Pitt (Defense #1), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/4 (Box 42, Reel 766)
      - 1986 Temple vs. Pitt (Offense #2), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/4 (Box 42, Reel 755)
      - 1986 Temple vs. Pitt (Offense #2), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/4 (Box 42, Reel 759)
      - 1986 Temple vs. Pitt (Defense #2), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/4 (Box 42, Reel 757)
      - 1986 Temple vs. Pitt (Defense #2), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/4 (Box 42, Reel 765)
      - 1986 Temple vs. Pitt (Kicking), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 579)
      - 1986 West Virginia vs. Pitt (Offense #1), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 744)
      - 1986 West Virginia vs. Pitt (Offense #1), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/4 (Box 42, Reel 767)
      - 1986 West Virginia vs. Pitt (Defense #1), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/4 (Box 42, Reel 769)
      - 1986 West Virginia vs. Pitt (Offense #2), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 738)
      - 1986 West Virginia vs. Pitt (Offense #2), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/4 (Box 42, Reel 768)
      - 1986 West Virginia vs. Pitt (Defense #2), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/4 (Box 42, Reel 770)
      - 1986 West Virginia vs. Pitt (Defense #2), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/4 (Box 42, Reel 771)
      - 1986 West Virginia vs. Pitt (Kicking), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 743)
      - 1987 Boston College vs. Pitt (Offense #1), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/4 (Box 42, Reel 789)
      - 1987 Boston College vs. Pitt (Offense #1), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/4 (Box 42, Reel 911)
      - 1987 Boston College vs. Pitt (Defense #1), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/4 (Box 42, Reel 792)
      - 1987 Boston College vs. Pitt (Offense #2), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/4 (Box 42, Reel 790)
      - 1987 Boston College vs. Pitt (Defense #2), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/4 (Box 42, Reel 793)
      - 1987 Boston College vs. Pitt (Offense #2), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/4 (Box 42, Reel 910)
      - 1987 Boston College vs. Pitt (Kicking), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/4 (Box 42, Reel 791)
      - 1987 Brigham Young vs. Pitt (Offense #1), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/4 (Box 42, Reel 783)
      - 1987 Brigham Young vs. Pitt (Offense #1), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/4 (Box 42, Reel 784)
      - 1987 Brigham Young vs. Pitt (Defense #1), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/4 (Box 42, Reel 781)
      - 1987 Brigham Young vs. Pitt (Offense #2), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/4 (Box 42, Reel 780)
      - 1987 Brigham Young vs. Pitt (Offense #2), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/4 (Box 42, Reel 894)
      - 1987 Brigham Young vs. Pitt (Defense #2), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/4 (Box 42, Reel 782)
      - 1987 Brigham Young vs. Pitt (Kicking), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/4 (Box 42, Reel 895)
      - 1987 Kent State vs. Pitt (Offense #1), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/4 (Box 42, Reel 801)
      - 1987 Kent State vs. Pitt (Defense #1), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/4 (Box 42, Reel 805)
      - 1987 Kent State vs. Pitt (Defense #1), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/4 (Box 42, Reel 808)
      - 1987 Kent State vs. Pitt (Offense #2), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/4 (Box 42, Reel 804)
      - 1987 Kent State vs. Pitt (Defense #2), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/4 (Box 42, Reel 806)
      - 1987 Kent State vs. Pitt (Defense #2), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/4 (Box 42, Reel 809)
      - 1987 Kent State vs. Pitt (Kicking), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/4 (Box 42, Reel 807)
      - 1987 Navy vs. Pitt (Offense #1), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/4 (Box 42, Reel 891)
      - 1987 Navy vs. Pitt (Offense #1), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/4 (Box 42, Reel 904)
      - 1987 Navy vs. Pitt (Defense #1), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/4 (Box 42, Reel 785)
      - 1987 Navy vs. Pitt (Offense #2), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/4 (Box 42, Reel 890)
      - 1987 Navy vs. Pitt (Offense #2), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/4 (Box 42, Reel 905)
      - 1987 Navy vs. Pitt (Defense #2), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/4 (Box 42, Reel 786)
      - 1987 Navy vs. Pitt (Defense #2), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/4 (Box 42, Reel 889)
      - 1987 Navy vs. Pitt (Kicking), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/4 (Box 42, Reel 787)
      - 1987 North Carolina State vs. Pitt (Offense #1), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/4 (Box 42, Reel 902)
      - 1987 North Carolina State vs. Pitt (Defense #1), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/4 (Box 42, Reel 761)
      - 1987 North Carolina State vs. Pitt (Defense #1), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/4 (Box 42, Reel 912)
      - 1987 North Carolina State vs. Pitt (Offense #2), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/3 (Box 42, Reel 574)
      - 1987 North Carolina State vs. Pitt (Defense #2), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/4 (Box 42, Reel 903)
      - 1987 North Carolina State vs. Pitt (Defense #2), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/4 (Box 42, Reel 913)
      - 1987 North Carolina State vs. Pitt (Kicking), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/4 (Box 42, Reel 897)
      - 1987 Notre Dame vs. Pitt (Defense #1), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/4 (Box 42, Reel 887)
      - 1987 Notre Dame vs. Pitt (Offense #2), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/4 (Box 42, Reel 888)
      - 1987 Notre Dame vs. Pitt (Defense #2), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/4 (Box 42, Reel 886)
      - 1987 Notre Dame vs. Pitt (Kicking), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/4 (Box 42, Reel 803)
      - 1987 Penn State vs. Pitt (Offense #1), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/4 (Box 42, Reel 874)
      - 1987 Penn State vs. Pitt (Defense #1), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/4 (Box 42, Reel 884)
      - 1987 Penn State vs. Pitt (Offense #2), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/4 (Box 42, Reel 885)
      - 1987 Penn State vs. Pitt (Defense #2), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/4 (Box 42, Reel 882)
      - 1987 Penn State vs. Pitt (Kicking), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/4 (Box 42, Reel 883)
      - 1987 Rutgers vs. Pitt (Offense #1), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/4 (Box 42, Reel 778)
      - 1987 Rutgers vs. Pitt (Offense #1), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/4 (Box 42, Reel 788)
      - 1987 Rutgers vs. Pitt (Defense #1), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/4 (Box 42, Reel 898)
      - 1987 Rutgers vs. Pitt (Defense #1), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/4 (Box 42, Reel 914)
      - 1987 Rutgers vs. Pitt (Offense #2), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/4 (Box 42, Reel 907)
      - 1987 Rutgers vs. Pitt (Offense #2), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/4 (Box 42, Reel 915)
      - 1987 Rutgers vs. Pitt (Defense #2), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/4 (Box 42, Reel 779)
      - 1987 Rutgers vs. Pitt (Defense #2), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/4 (Box 42, Reel 899)
      - 1987 Rutgers vs. Pitt (Kicking), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/4 (Box 42, Reel 777)
      - 1987 Syracuse vs. Pitt (Defense #1), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/4 (Box 42, Reel 896)
      - 1987 Syracuse vs. Pitt (Defense #1), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/4 (Box 42, Reel 901)
      - 1987 Syracuse vs. Pitt (Defense #2), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/4 (Box 42, Reel 900)
      - 1987 Syracuse vs. Pitt (Defense #2), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/4 (Box 42, Reel 916)
      - 1987 Syracuse vs. Pitt (Kicking), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/4 (Box 42, Reel 917)
      - 1987 Temple vs. Pitt (Offense #1), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/4 (Box 42, Reel 794)
      - 1987 Temple vs. Pitt (Offense #1), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/4 (Box 42, Reel 906)
      - 1987 Temple vs. Pitt (Defense #1), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/4 (Box 42, Reel 795)
      - 1987 Temple vs. Pitt (Defense #1), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/4 (Box 42, Reel 908)
      - 1987 Temple vs. Pitt (Offense #2), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/4 (Box 42, Reel 798)
      - 1987 Temple vs. Pitt (Offense #2), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/4 (Box 42, Reel 918)
      - 1987 Temple vs. Pitt (Defense #2), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/4 (Box 42, Reel 796)
      - 1987 Temple vs. Pitt (Defense #2), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/4 (Box 42, Reel 909)
      - 1987 Temple vs. Pitt (Kicking), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/4 (Box 42, Reel 797)
      - 1987 Texas vs. Pitt-Blue Bonnet Bowl (Offense #1), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/4 (Box 42, Reel 879)
      - 1987 Texas vs. Pitt-Blue Bonnet Bowl (Defense #1), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/4 (Box 42, Reel 877)
      - 1987 Texas vs. Pitt-Blue Bonnet Bowl (Offense #2), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/4 (Box 42, Reel 878)
      - 1987 Texas vs. Pitt-Blue Bonnet Bowl (Defense #2), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/4 (Box 42, Reel 876)
      - 1987 Texas vs. Pitt-Blue Bonnet Bowl (Kicking), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/4 (Box 42, Reel 875)
      - 1987 West Virginia vs. Pitt (Offense #1), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/4 (Box 42, Reel 892)
      - 1987 West Virginia vs. Pitt (Defense #1), 16mm film Media Room 6/6/4 (Box 42, Reel 799)
      - 1987 West Virginia vs. Pitt (Defense #1), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/4 (Box 42, Reel 893)
      - 1987 West Virginia vs. Pitt (Offense #2), 16mm film Media Room 5/6/4 (Box 42, Reel 881)